What Mrs. Robinson did is no comparison to what Mrs. Potter does in this film!
Career Bed is a drama film directed by Joel M. Reed.
A mother is determined that her daughter will be a movie star, and will do
anything--and have her daughter do anything--to make it happen.
Susan (as Lisa Duran), played by Jennifer Welles.
Mrs. Potter, played by Honey Hunter.
Jack Landive, played by John Cardoza.
Gerald (as Stidge Glisspayne), played by Stioge Glyspayne.
Bob, played by John David.
Pendulum is a 1969 American neo noir crime thriller film directed by George
Schaefer and starring George Peppard, Jean Seberg and Richard Kiley.
It was one of a series of medium budgeted genre
movies Peppard made around this time.
The film explores themes of lesbian sex, lgbt, casting
couch, mother daughter relationship, lesbian.
The tone is emotional.